Saya-chan, I still don't have enough of what I said earlier.
せやちゃん、ちょっとまだ、さっきのやつ足りない
Not enough.
足りない
Not enough?
足りない?
Even though there were so many people.
あんなに大人数やったのに
There's still a little bit of everyone left,
ちょっとまだみんな残ってくれてるんで、
For a second helping.
おかわりで
However, it's the same as before,
ただ、さっきと同じであれなんで、
Something a little different to play,
ちょっと変わったプレイ的なものを、
Let's all have a little fun with Mataseya-chan.
ちょっとみんなで、またせやちゃんにいっぱい楽しんでもらおう
Kana and.
かな と
yes.
はい
So let's all vote.
じゃあ、みなさんに投票してもらいましょう
I want you to be more and more satisfied.
もっともっと満足してもらうように
Let me make you feel better now.
さっき気持ちよくしてもらおうね
Somehow, no.
なんかさ、ダメ
I mean, it's not that heavy.
なんかさ、重たんないっていうか、
I want more stimulation.
も っと刺激は欲しいって
picture?
え?
Won't you take it?
取らない?
No.
ダメ
It's not okay to do normal things.
普通なことじゃダメ
I'm not satisfied.
満足できない
There are three after all.
やっぱり3つな
Then you can do something you've never done before.
じゃあ、やったことないようなことをやれるじゃん
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Whatever happens, don't tell me anymore.
どうなったらもう言わないでよ
Keep that smile on your face until the end.
その笑顔をずっと最後まで
I feel like I'm going to laugh though.
笑っちゃう気がするけど
Well then.
じゃあ
Yeah?
うん?
Ah, I'm already talking while I come.
あ、もう喋りながら来ちゃう
Do you know?
知ってる?
Like this.
こんなん
I don't really understand what you're saying.
ちょっと何言ってるかわからない
piece.
ピース
Yeah.
うん
Ah, so cute.
あ、 かわいい
Yeah.
うん
Let it drip loosely.
ゆだりだらだら垂らしてね
Leave it like this.
このまま
Danger dripped.
ダンジャー垂らしちゃって
Yeah.
うん
Because my nose is blowing.
鼻吹いてるから
Yeah.
うん
What is this?
なんだこれ
Yeah.
うん
I have no idea what you're saying though.
何言ってるか全然わからないけど
a little bit.
ちょっと
Chew it properly.
ちゃん とちょっと噛んで
Wait, what?
ちょっと何?
I don't know what you're saying.
何言ってるかわからない
Chest, chest.
チェスト、チェスト
Ah, that's great.
あ、最高
Hime is the best.
ひめ最高
Hmm, Hanhan.
うーん、ハンハン
What are you saying?
何言ってる?
I'm not hungry.
お腹は空いてない
Show me.
見せてよ
a~~~~~~~~.
あ〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
a~~~~~.
あ〜〜〜〜〜
Please excuse me and follow this.
これ、失礼ながら従いで
I've finally come to this place.
ついにこんなところに来ちゃったんだ
Yeah.
うん
Please show me your strange face, please.
ちょっと変な顔見せてください、ほら
Look at the grinning face.
にくり顔、ほら
rude.
失礼
Yeah.
うん
That's just boring, isn't it?
これだけじゃさ、 つまらないでしょ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You can't do anything.
何もできないでしょ
picture?
え?
I'm not hungry, it's okay.
お腹が空いてない、大丈夫
a~~~~~~~.
あ〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
This is stable below.
これさ、下、安定になってますね
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
What happened?
あれ、どうした?
He can't do anything.
何もできないやつだね
Yeah.
うん
I don't know what it is though.
何かわかんないけど
Unfortunately not anymore.
残念ながらもう
He can't do anything.
何もできないやつだね
Good.
よいな
That's what he says.
言うらしいよ
I want to tease you like this.
いじめたいね、こんなの
Yeah.
うん
Don't you have a nerve?
神 経つないのか?
Are you nervous?
神経つないのか?
Yeah.
うん
It seems like he's nervous.
神経つるらしいよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
I did it backwards.
逆にしてのしちゃったの
Yeah.
うん
Look, I was licking it.
ほら、ベロベロした
I licked it.
ベロベロした
Because I can't do anything.
何もできないから
Look.
ほら
It's okay to lick it.
ベロベロしていいですよ
I feel tired and lonely.
くさむき寂しいって
It seems lonely here too.
こっちも寂しいらしい
Hey.
ねえ
This one is a little bit.
こっちが少し
Yeah.
うん
what happened?
どうしたの?
どう したの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I've missed the spittle of my comb.
く しのツバが寂しちゃったんだから
what happened?
どうしたの?
Did you miss your comb?
くしが寂しかった?
It went in really well.
もちもち入ったよ
ah.
あー
a,
あ、
I feel lonely.
寂 し出されるって
You felt lonely.
寂し出されたね
Saa-chan, I just want to do it.
さあちゃん、ちょっとおそらくおそらくしちゃいたい
Yes, I'm leaving.
はい、もういくって
what happened?
どうしたの?
Look where.
どこ見て
Come on, let me take a breather.
さあちゃん、ちょっと息んでもらおう
Because I feel lonely towards the children who are close to me.
なんか近い子に寂し出てくるから
It came out, it came out.
出てきた、出てきた
Ah, that's naughty.
あー、やらしい
For those who went right away, go ahead.
さっそく行った人、さっそく
Right away, he wants to show off a little more.
さっそく、もうちょっと見せたがいになるんだって
Yes, there are people on the platform, on the platform.
そう、ホームに人いるよ、ホームに
Look, look.
見て、見て
Look at me.
こっち見てって
Did you notice?
気づいた?
Yeah.
うん
Did you see it?
見てた?
Did you notice?
気づいた?
real?
ほんと?
I noticed, I noticed.
気づいた、気づいた
Come here.
こっち来てって
ah.
あー
Come here.
こっち来てって
I just came.
ちょっと 来ちゃった
I put it out.
出したよ
It's close to my stomach, but let me breathe.
お腹近いけど、息んでもらおう
a,
あ、
Look, it's out, it's out, it's out.
ほ ら、出た、出た、出た
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
Stand up, I want to show you more.
立ってよ、もっと見せたがいよ
I cleaned it up, and now it's over there.
お掃除してあげて、今、あっちに
Hey, push it up and see.
ほら、押し上げてほら
It has to be close now.
もう、近いといけない
Push, push.
押し、押し
You can stand.
立っていいよ
Add, add, add.
立て、加えて、加えて
So they let me in.
それで入れてもらえた
Let me show you.
見せてあげて
Here, get your hands on it.
こっち、手ついて
Get your hands on it, get your hands on it.
手ついて、手ついて
Wow, there's someone looking at me.
うわ、なんか、あ、こっち見てる人いるね
Let me see, here.
見てあげて、ほら
Clean it up.
お掃除しあげて
calm down.
落 ち 着いて
Did you enjoy showing it again?
また、見せ満喫した?
Did you see it?
見てくれた?
I'm tired.
つって
Are you watching?
見てるかな?
This guy isn't waving his hand at me.
手振りかけてるんじゃないの、この人
Over here.
こっち上で
I feel like I'm watching.
見てる気がする
I feel like that.
気がするよね
Amazing, I'm watching.
すごい、見てる
Call me properly, call me.
ちゃんと呼んで、呼んで
Over here.
こっち上で
There might be someone next.
次の人がいるかもしれないね
That guy doesn't even play the field.
あの奴がフィールドもしないよ
Do you want to change location?
ちょっと、場所変える?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's go separately.
じゃあ、別行こうか
Shall we do it here?
ここでする?
It's down.
下になってます
What do you think?
どうですか?
Is Chibakushin okay?
ちばくしんさんは大丈夫?
Yeah, yeah.
うん、 うん
Okay.
よし
Look at the bottom.
下が、ほら見てほら
Water, bottom.
水で、下が
Please take care of Tink.
チンク気にしてあげて
Clean the next person.
次の人を、お掃除してあげて
Let me clean it for you.
お掃除してあげて
This person.
こっちの人
Look, I'm stuck.
ほら、チンクつまった
Of the body?
体の?
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's out, it's out, it's out.
出てる出てる出てる
Kimi-chan, come on.
きみちゃん、おいで
Lick it, Osson Sugar.
舐めて、オッソンシュガー
Leave it alone for a while.
ちょっと置いてあげてよ
Should I go as is or should I put my dick in?
そのまま行くのか、ちんこ入れるのか、
Put it in your pussy
まんこ入れる
Of?
の か
put in?
入れる?
Do you want to put it on your hair?
髪にかけたいかな
I wonder if I'll let you.
させるかな
Let's get it out.
出そう
Mainly
おも
ERROR
ろ い
I feel really bad.
すごく気持ち悪い
Do you feel better now?
今も気持ちよくなった?
How was it, Sena-chan?
せなちゃん、どうだった?
I'm satisfied now.
もう、満足
Enough?
もういい?
Are you okay now, Chinkin?
もう、チンキン、大丈夫?
Are you okay now?
もう大丈夫?
Wouldn't you say something like that?
そんな発言しない?
To this boyfriend.
この彼氏さんに
Back then, it wasn't hard to get a little spin, right?
あの時、ちょっとスピンでもなかなかいなかったんじゃない?
No.
ないです
It was already difficult.
もう大変だったんです
Have you had enough sex for the rest of your life?
もう、一生分くらいセックスした?
did.
した
Have you made many friends?
いっぱい仲良しされた?
I'm enduring it.
耐えてきてる
Are you enduring it?
耐えてきてる?
下側
Are you enduring it?
耐えてきてる?
Yeah.
うん
How much sex do you want to do?
どれだけの性子をやりたい?
No, I have to consult with you a lot.
いや、もう、結構相談しないと
I want to do it a lot.
いっぱいやりたいよね
that's right.
そうです
Well then, let's get down to it.
さあね、じゃあ、ちょうかくんなところで
I hope you get lots of comments.
いっぱいコメントくるといいね
Please watch a lot.
たくさん見てください
Please look at it a lot.
たくさん見てくださいって
Well, everyone, now that you're feeling better.
じゃあ、みんなね、気持ちよくなったところで
How many books have you read in total?
合計何冊ぐらいしてんだっけ?
It's over 20.
20は超えてる
That's terrible.
やばいね
I agree.
そうだね
Alone.
1人でね
It's a big deal.
大したもんだ
see you later.
じゃあ、またね
See you soon, or rather, just to the viewers.
またねっていうか、 ちょっと視聴者さんにね、
Let's comment.
コメントあおろうね
yes.
はい
now?
今?
No, I mean now, please take a look.
いや、今っていうか、見てもらってね、
Let me judge.
判断してもらおう
Oh, sure.
ああ、確かに
Well then, bye.
じゃあ、バイバイ
Thank you.
ありがとね
yes.
はい
Bye bye.
バイバーイ
Huh?
あれ?
Sena-chan?
セナちゃん?
Oh, it's Sena-chan.
あ、セナちゃんだね
That's quite different, Kakko.
だいぶ違うな、かっこ
It's completely off.
完全オフだね
I agree.
そうですね
what up?
どうした?
I have something important to talk about.
ちょっと、大事な話があって
Are you going to a press store?
記者店とか行く?
Let's take a photo.
写真撮ろう
Oh, no, not at all.
あ、いや、全然
It's okay there.
そこで大丈夫
Yeah.
うん
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
picture?
え?
What is this?
なにこれ?
The herring one?
ニシンのやつ?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Echo photo.
エコー写真
What, you mean you gave me a red herring?
え、ニシンしましたってこと?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
After taking pictures for the last 10 days, it's a bit...
この間の10日撮ってから、 ちょっとまあ、
I thought it was symbolic, so how did you feel when you took that photo?
象徴的にあれだなって思って、 その写真が行ったらどうでした?
What is that?
それなに?
So what week is it?
それで言ったら何週目なんでしょう?
Week 4.
4週目
Just finished it?
出来たばっかり?
that's right.
そうです
ah.
あー
Eh, so?
え、で?
I need to take responsibility.
責任撮っていただかないとな
Do you want me to take responsibility?
責任撮ってほしいの?
To me?
俺に?
Please show me one more time.
ちょっともう一回見せて
Well, from my uncle's point of view.
じゃあ、おじさんからしたら
yes.
はい
I did shoot 10P, but was it possible to do it with 10P?
10P確かに撮ったけど、10Pで出来た?
Maybe not.
ないかもしれないじゃん
After all, it's being done elsewhere, right?
だって他でやってるでしょ?
So there's a possibility.
だから、その可能性もあるじゃん
yes.
はい
So what do you think?
だから、どうなの?
I think so, but what do you think?
とも思うんだけど、 どうなの?
Even now, do you mean the timing?
今でも、 時期的にっていうこと?
I agree.
そうですね
In terms of timing.
時期的には
If I have to say one more thing, I wonder if she might actually be pregnant.
もう一つ言うんであれば、 本当に妊娠してるかもどうか、
I thought it was dangerous.
俺は危ういと思ってて
If you're talking about glorious photos, then...
栄光写真とかっていうのは、そこまで言うんだったら、
I guess it's true, but
本当なんだろうけど、
There's also the possibility that someone might bring a glorified photo of a child that isn't their own.
自 分の子じゃない栄光写真とか持ってきちゃう可能性もあるわけ
Well then.
じゃ ん
So, can I do a pregnancy test in front of my uncle?
じゃあ、おじさんの前で妊娠検査役とか出来る?
But it can be done.
でも、出来ます
Well then, let's go buy it now.
じゃあ、買いに行こうか、今から
Well then, I'll go buy it.
じゃあ、買いに行くよ
Teacher, come here.
先生のちゃん、こっちに行って
yes.
はい
So, do you want to stay alone?
じゃあ、一人にすんの?
this?
これ?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, that's fine.
じゃあ、それでいいよ
So how much?
じゃあ、いくら?
1094 yen.
1094円
Hey, let's go further.
ちょっと、ちょっともっと行く
heavy.
重い
1100 yen.
1100円
yes.
はい
I'll give it to you.
渡すから
yes.
はい
I'll give it to you.
渡すから
1200 yen.
1200円ね
yes.
はい
Just buy some of this.
これでちょっと、買ってきて
yes.
はい
Buy it.
買ってきて
Did you buy it?
買った?
I bought it.
買いました
Show me.
見せてよ
You can do it for 3 times.
3回分出来んじゃん
Well, once you do that, there's a toilet over there.
じゃあ、そしたら1回、あっちにトイレあるから
yes.
はい
Then go over there for a while.
そしたらあっちでちょっと行ってきてよ
yes.
はい
Have you come?
来た?
Did you do it?
出来た?
I went.
行きました
Come here.
こっち来て
Did you do it?
出来た?
yes.
はい
Show me.
見せてよ
Seriously?
マジ?
yes.
はい
Why do you want that?
どうして欲しいの、それ?
Is that what it feels like?
そんな感じ?
Yeah.
うん
oh dear,
まあ、
Well then, let's think about it for a moment.
ちょっと じゃあ、 ちょっと考える?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
I'll think about it, then.
考えるわ、それで
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well, just a little bit, Sena-chan.
まあ、ちょっとさ、セナちゃんのさ、
There are fans, after all.
ファンとかもさ、やっぱりいるからさ
What do you think?
思うの?
I need some time to think.
ちょっと考える時間が欲しいです
Well, that's right.
まあ、そうだね
There's still time to think.
考える時間はまだあるから
No, singing today and tomorrow,
いや、歌も今日は明日とかにはさ、
I can't reply right away, but I might think about it.
すぐには返事できないけど、ちょっと考えるかもしれない
It's been a while since the video hasn't been released yet.
この間のさ、だって動画もさ、まだ出してないしさ
So I thought I'd put it out there and think about it a little.
だから出して、ちょっと考えようかなっていうのもあるから
So, yeah.
それで、 うん
Hey, isn't it kind of cute?
ちょっとさ、なんか可愛いの?
That look.
その格好なんか
All I have to do is talk.
話しかあるけど
It's quite a loungewear.
結構、部屋着ですね
picture?
え?
Room wear?
部屋着?
In room wear.
部屋着で
Okay, let's take a commemorative photo then.
ちょっとじゃあ、 はい、じゃあ記念撮影で
At the commemorative photo shoot, I took out that, that, that.
記念撮影で、あの、 あれ、あれ出して
That guy in charge of inspecting sewing machines.
あの、ミシン検査役のやつ
yes.
そう
Look at the photo like this.
と、こう写真見して
yes.
そう
So, let's put it on top of that.
それで、じゃあその上に置いて
yes.
そう
Look at that.
それ見して
yes.
はい
So, turn this way.
で、こっち向いて
Well then,
じゃあ、
OK
Well then, uncle, I'll deal with it.
じゃあ 一応、じゃあおじさん、それで対応するから
So, I'll contact you again.
だからじゃあ、 また連絡するから
Thank you for coming this far.
わざわざありがとね、ここまで来てくれて
Yeah.
うん
Well, don't get too carried away.
まあ、あんまりさ、やまないでよ
hey.
ね
I'll get back to you in a bit, this guy.
ちょっとまた連絡するよ、こいつ
hey.
ね
bye bye.
バイバイ